{
    "subject": "resource/Dori_Caymmi",
    "predicate": "property/associatedActs",
    "object": "resource/Danilo_Caymmi",
    "human_readable": "Dori Caymmi was associated with Danilo Caymmi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9837643504142761,
            "question": "Were Dori Caymmi and Danilo Caymmi related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9653493762016296,
            "question": "Who was Dori Caymmi associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.964015781879425,
            "question": "Are there any famous works associated with either Dori Caymmi or Danilo Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9516683220863342,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Dori Caymmi and Danilo Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149042367935181,
            "question": "Are there any historical accounts or biographies about Dori and Danilo Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6942746043205261,
            "question": "How did Dori Caymmi contribute to the arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6712462902069092,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Danilo Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5851037502288818,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Dori Caymmi and music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5820947289466858,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the artistic legacy of Danilo Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46636781096458435,
            "question": "What is known about Dori Caymmi's life and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dori Caymmi was associated with Danilo Caymmi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_631_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the artistic legacy of Danilo Caymmi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_631_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between Dori Caymmi and music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_631_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Danilo Caymmi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_631_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_631_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can see that:\n\n* There are documents about Dori Caymmi and Danilo Caymmi, which suggests a familial relationship between them.\n* In fact, both documents mention Dori Caymmi as the son of composer Dorival Caymmi, who is not mentioned in the same documents but might be related to Danilo Caymmi.\n\nGiven this context, I would say that the information supports the triple that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis means that Dori Caymmi was associated with Danilo Caymmi."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention multiple collaborations and associations between Dori Caymmi and Danilo Caymmi, indicating they were indeed associated. Examples include their shared works such as \"Pot-Pourri: Sereia / Rainha do Mar\" and \"Marina - Ao Vivo No Rio De Janeiro / 1987\", further supporting the association."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}